allleftturns.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy - NASCAR

Effective as of June 1, 2010

At allleftturns.com committed to respecting people’s privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our website. In order to do so, we may gather certain personal information about you. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our website. By using allleftturns.com, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in this Policy, and you signify your agreement to the AllLeftTurns(ALT) Privacy Policy.

**Information submitted by you for inclusion on your AllLeftTurns profile.**

nformation, pictures and media files you upload to your account (“Submissions”) will be posted on the site, subject to our Users Terms and Conditionsand accessible by all visitors to the site (unless you expressly restrict such access through your account settings), and _ALT_ has no control over, and shall incur no responsibility for, how such visitors will use such Submissions. _ALT_ reserves the right (but not the obligation) to remove or edit Submissions, but does not regularly review Submissions.

We may offer chat, user reviews, multi-player games, bulletin board, or other public functions and any posting by you is considered public information available to other users. Any posting is governed by our Terms of Use. You should take care to not use personal information in your screen name or other information that might be publicly available to other users.

Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of the website, such as in online forums or chat rooms, such information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of the website.

**What information does** _ ** _ALT_**_ **collect?**

When you visit allleftturns.com, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes which pages are visited and any feedback from our visitors. We then aggregate this information with other pieces of information to improve our site and make your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible.  
When you register for the website, we collect personal information such as name, age, and email in order to set up your account.

In addition to the information we collect upon your initial registration with allleftturns.com, we may ask you for personal information at other times, including, but not limited to, when you enter promotions or contests, and when you respond to a survey.

Upon cancelling your AllLeftTurns account, you have the right to request deletion of your account information, subject to our need to keep appropriate archives for our business operations.

For reasons such as improving member experience and providing customized communications to our users, we may receive information about you from third party sources and our web logs and add it to the information that we have received from you. Web logs automatically record anything a web server sees, which may include e-mail addresses you enter into a form or pages viewed by a user at a particular IP address.

We maintain archives of our web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after we delete the information from its active database. We maintain archives for disaster recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

**1.   **It is used to set up and maintain your allleftturns.com account. If you provide us with your mobile phone information, we may use such information to communicate with you regarding allleftturns.com by SMS, MMS, text message or other electronic means to a mobile device.

**2.** Your phone number may be used in the event that our customer service representatives need to contact you and cannot reach you by email.

**3.** Your personal information will never be sold to any other website owner or merchant. We hate junk mail as much as you. This is why we will only send you email about items that we feel you should know about. This includes special promotional items that _ALT_ endorses, membership changes, terms and conditions changes, Holiday cards, and the latest happenings on allleftturns.com. When we send you emails that include a link to the website, that link may contain an alphanumeric identifier that allows us to identify the person to whom we sent the message so that we can personalize our content for that individual.

**Email Opt-out**

Users who no longer wish to receive our email updates or other notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the applicable email or by logging-in and changing their account settings.

**With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?**

_ALT_ does not sell, rent, or trade any personally identifying information with others. However, when one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest with the co-sponsor(s). If we intend to share such information, you will be notified prior to the collection of that information. If you do not want your information to be shared, you will be able to choose not to allow the transfer by not using or signing up for that particular service, promotion or contest.

We may also share aggregate user information in a non-personally identifiable manner with advertisers and other third parties in order to present to users more targeted advertising, products and services.

We may contract with third parties to conduct research and marketing on our behalf. Such third parties will be fully bound by an obligation of confidentiality to _ALT_ and may not use any personally-identifiable information provided by us other than as expressly instructed by us and in strict compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect from you with outside records (e.g., information we obtain from other companies, including wireless providers) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. To fulfill your requests for products and services (e.g., provide you with content via your mobile phone), we may share the personally identifiable information you provide with your mobile phone service provider or their partner and subcontractor companies. Our privacy policy does not cover such entities’ use of information. To learn more about your provider’s privacy practices, you should consult its privacy policy.

**What information do parties other than _ALT_ collect?**

Some entities that have links on our site may collect personally identifying information about you when you access or utilize those links. _ALT_ does not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those advertisers and websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

It is important to note that those entities may not follow the same privacy policies as _ALT_. For instance, if you click on an advertisement on allleftturns.com, you may be taken away from allleftturns.com to an entirely different site. These links can also be from advertisers, content providers and/or partners who may use allleftturns.com’s logo and/or style as a result of a co-branding agreement yet they may still not follow the same privacy policies as _ALT_.

Applications you use or download from our site may contain third party digital rights management systems (“DRMS”) which may allow for communication between your software and the third party and utilize security features (e.g., preventing distribution of or access to the applications in the event of unauthorized use). These DRMS are subject to their own license agreements and you agree that we shall not be responsible for any loss or damage of any sort relating to the use of the DRMS or your dealings with such third parties. The applications may also contain DRMS produced by us which allow for communication between the applications you use or download and our systems and which collect information describing your computer system in order to prevent illegal or unauthorized use of the applications.

**What are** **“cookies” and “web beacons”** **and how do we use them?**

Our site may use “cookies” and “web beacons” to speed navigation, keep track of items, and provide you with custom-tailored services. A “web beacon”is an embedded GIF file that specifically helps us track whether you have viewed a specific piece of content. We also use “cookies” to remember information you gave us so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit the site. By showing us how and when visitors use the site, “cookies” and “web beacons” help us see which site areas and content are popular and which are not. We also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to any sponsors.Some advertisers or websites that have links on our site may also use their own “cookies.”

Most browsers are initially set to accept “cookies.” If you’d prefer, you can set yours to refuse “cookies.” You will not be able to use our service if you turn off the “cookies” option.

**Security**

Our member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. In addition, we use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff.

However, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of our member information at any time.

**COPPA compliance**

Our site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We assume products purchased through credit card means are purchased by adults. We have designed this privacy policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third parties.

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail or postal mail as listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after we delete the information from its active database.

We believe that parents should supervise their children’s online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission.

**Business transitions  **

In the event _ALT_ goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Users Located Outside of the United States**

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov). For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/)

We make an effort to protect the personal information of all users of allleftturns.com. If you are unsure whether this privacy policy is in conflict with the rules applicable where you are located, you should not submit your personal information to allleftturns.com. **IN ADDITION, IF YOU ARE LOCATED WITHIN THE EUROPEAN UNION, YOU SHOULD NOTE THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, THE LAWS OF WHICH MAY BE DEEMED BY THE EUROPEAN UNION TO HAVE INADEQUATE DATA PROTECTION.** Users of allleftturns.com located in countries outside of the United States who submit personal information do thereby consent to the transfer of that information to and/or storage of the information in the United States.

**Cooperation with law enforcement; fraud protection**

_ALT_ fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to disclose information about members who we believe are in violation of applicable laws or regulations, or as required to respond to a subpoena, court orders or other legal process requiring such disclosure. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful and to exchange information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used or collected. From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy and will notify you of those changes by email or post a notice on the allleftturns.com website. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use allleftturns.com after such changes have been first posted. Please note that if you opt out of receiving legal notices from us, those legal notices will still govern your use of allleftturns.com, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.
